http://www.initialimages.co.uk/privacy-policy

Shopping Basket0 items £0.00View ItemsCheckoutLogin | RegisterCall us on 0191 455 8128HomeAbout UsContact UsCategoriesBest SellersPersonalised GiftsSchool UniformsPopular CategoriesSportswearT-ShirtsPolo ShirtsSweatshirtsCorporatewearWorkwearFleecesHoodiesJacketsHats0191 455 8128Home > Privacy Policy & Conditions Privacy Policy We are committed to protecting our customers’ privacy, and we do our best to be transparent about the information we collect from website users. Please review this policy for your peace of mind. 1. Information RequestsIf you would like to view the information (if any) that we hold on you, please email sales@initialimages.co.uk. We aim to respond to information requests within 1 month of receipt. Any inaccuracies you report to us will be rectified as quickly as possible, and we will usually be happy to delete your personal information upon request (except in special circumstances). 2. Your Information & How We Use ItIf you place an order via the Initial Images Embroidery Ltd website, you will be required to input the following information: Your email addressYour first name and surnameYour billing addressYour delivery address You may also provide us with additional information if you wish – for example, you will have the option to input the name of your company if you are ordering on behalf of a business. All of the details you enter during the purchasing process are collected for the sole purpose of processing and dispatching your order. Additionally, we may contact you after your products have been delivered to ask you to review your experience. You will not be added to any mailing lists without your permission, and we will not send you any correspondence that is not related to your Initial Images Embroidery Ltd order. If you choose to contact us using the enquiry form on our website, we will collect the following information: Your nameYour email addressYour telephone numberYour address (optional)Any other information you choose to supply in the body of your message This information is collected for the sole purpose of processing and responding to your enquiry. Again, you will not be added to any mailing lists without your permission, and we will not send you any correspondence that is unrelated to your enquiry. We try to ensure that all personal information we hold is accurate and up to date. We hold this information securely and in accordance with the relevant laws, including the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). 3. Artwork & BrandingIf you place an order via the Initial Images Embroidery Ltd website, you may have the option to add artwork / branding to the garments you are purchasing. Any images / designs you submit to Initial Images Embroidery Ltd – either via email or the uploader tool on our website – will be kept private and not shared with any unaffiliated third parties. We will never use your artwork / branding for any purpose other than the fulfilment of your order. 4. Payment DetailsThis website uses Sage Pay to process online payments securely. Your card details are never stored by Initial Images Embroidery Ltd, and all details are transferred using SSL encryption. 5. Our Mailing ListWhen you contact Initial Images Embroidery Ltd or place an order via our website, you will have the option to join our mailing list. Subscribers are sent promotional emails containing product information, special offers, and other updates from Initial Images Embroidery Ltd. We use MailChimp to manage our mailing list. Subscribers can unsubscribe from our mailing list at any time by clicking the ‘unsubscribe’ link that appears in all of the promotional emails we send. If you give us permission to add you to our mailing list, we will never share your email with other organisations or send you any emails that are not relevant to Initial Images Embroidery Ltd. 6. Google AnalyticsLike many website owners, we use Google Analytics to anonymously monitor traffic and user behaviour on our website. This tool does not collect any personally identifiable information. However, if you do not want to be included in our Analytics data, you can opt out of Google Analytics using this browser add-on. 7. Cookies PolicyThis website uses cookies to improve your online experience. Click here to view our cookies policy. 8. Fraud PreventionWe take the risk of internet fraud very seriously. If we believe that an order has been placed fraudulently or that our website has been abused in any way, we reserve the right to share information with third party fraud prevention companies (including banks) and the police. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please email sales@initialimages.co.uk.CorporatewearMensWomensAccessoriesFleecesMensKidsWomensHatsCapsKnitted And WoolyBeaniesMorfsHoodiesMensWomensKidsUnisexJacketsMensWomensKidsPolo ShirtsMensWomensKidsSportswearTrainingFootballRugbyGolfCricketSweatshirtsMensWomensKidsT-ShirtsMensWomensKidsWorkwearHi VizPolos And SweatsFleecesTrousersJacketsBootsOverallsAccessoriesTerms | Privacy Policy | Cookies Policy | About Us | Contact Us | Site MapEcommerce Websites by Designer Websites Ltd Copyright © 2020 Initial Images Embroidery Ltd Powered by:
